Guide to the Jack Doroshow / Flawless Sabrina Papers MSS.594
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI. Personal, 1937-2018; 8 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversize box, and 1 shared cassette box; 1 audiocassette; 603 Megabytes in 1 recording file
  - "A Bona Fide Croaker: An Autobiography of Doctor Benway by Violet the Baboon" -- Author Unknown, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - John Gallagher Sketchbook, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Previously Framed Note / Poem by "Bob", undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - William Burroughs -- Image and Writing re: Him, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - List of Items in Storage (from Jack's Apartment?), undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Items from Disassembled Wall Display in Jack's Apartment, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Photograph by Cam McDonald -- Portrait of Jack Doroshow "Bunny's Honey", undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Audio Recording of Telephone Conversation re: Renting and Care of Doroshow Property, undated (Box Shared Fales 094, Audiocassette 594_006)